<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Our course modules on AIT TR static site</title><link>https://kolya-ya.github.io/edTech-hugo/en/modules/</link><description>Recent content in Our course modules on AIT TR static site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kolya-ya.github.io/edTech-hugo/en/modules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Basic course</title><link>https://kolya-ya.github.io/edTech-hugo/en/modules/base/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kolya-ya.github.io/edTech-hugo/en/modules/base/</guid><description>The training begins with the Basic course, where you will get general knowledge about information technologies, programming, stages of program development.
You will write your first projects and understand the basics of OOP (object-oriented programming).
You will be able to make an informed decision regarding the direction in which you will continue your studies.</description></item><item><title>Professional course</title><link>https://kolya-ya.github.io/edTech-hugo/en/modules/professional/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kolya-ya.github.io/edTech-hugo/en/modules/professional/</guid><description>After the general (2 months) professional course, during which you learn the technologies needed to work in a modern company, you diverge into the Specializations and learn the frameworks necessary for professional activity:
Full-stack specialization Automated QA testing specialization</description></item><item><title>Project</title><link>https://kolya-ya.github.io/edTech-hugo/en/modules/project/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kolya-ya.github.io/edTech-hugo/en/modules/project/</guid><description>After the academic part, you start your 2 months-long project.
Your project will allow you to demonstrate experience in developing or testing modern applications during the employment process.
After the academic course and internship you will receive group and individual consultations on how to write a CV and prepare for interviews and test assignments.
With the support of our partners, German and Israeli companies UpTeam /USA/, CloudGeometry /USA/, Initech /Israel/, Adastra /Czech-Germany/, Itolium /Germany/ — you will put a real line in your resume, which will help you find a permanent job.</description></item></channel></rss>